We rang in the morning chimes, we
And we're consolidating.
Is that right?
I'll get back on track.
We are the morning chimes.
This is Stacy Chimes Stuhl.
Yes, this is America, attendance number three.
And the number three is Keith Blow... and the number three is Misie Hoshina.
Yes, that's right.
This time
We are visiting a Korean restaurant, Real.
This is your first location on YouTube!
Yay!
That's great.
Try it. In here.
Let it glow.
It's glowing.
What was that?
I'm lost.
This time it's us.
Hayashi SPF tripe.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!Oh, my God.
There's something else on the menu, though.
Yes, there is.
Can someone tell me what's on it?
It's okay.
Hayashi SPF Thick-Cut Triangle Sal.
And the Hayashi SPF Moku-Saru!
I love mokuzaru!
And kangjangseu!
I love kangjangseu!
Thank you so much for letting me try it!
Oh, I am!
But I'm so confused!
There's too much pickled radish!
Are you still going to order it?
I'll go eat some more takumi next time!
I'll do that.
I want some more takuman!
You're the best, Mirie.
So many things.
She wants to eat this and that.
How old were you once... when you were about 15?
When I was 16.
Some kind of restaurant with good cheese risotto.
It's the one you recommended.Mirie recommended it.
I'll come with my family.
When we went there
I ordered a lot of things.
I thought, "I'll never be able to eat all that.
And then all the kids around the age of Ouchiuchi...
They're all gone now.
I had to play with them.
So we had to play by ourselves.
That's when we started playing.
That's when we started to play together.
"I want to eat this, I want to eat that...
I couldn't stop her.
She wanted to share everything with me.
But lately, she's been trying to stop me.
Then you wouldn't be able to eat it.
The rest was just a bunch of beehives.
What do we do?
There's this pop-up that's all the rage in Korea.
There's a beehive with the beehive cut out of it.
Heh.
Maya, you're going to work later.
She said she has to work.
Not today.Not today.
I don't think I'm a non-fan.
It's been a while since we've had Korean food like this, right?
It's been a while.
It's been a while since we ate together.
When was the last time we ate together?
I wonder.
Isn't it that time?
Only ramen in Hiroshima.
Hiroshima... my favorite restaurant, Hanaichi Mombé.
I just happened to run into a fan.
I happened to run into a fan.
He was a fan of Hanaichi Mombé.
But he probably wasn't there for the spring tour.
He was outside.
I wonder what Carp's
Maybe Carp was there for the completion of the tour.
There might be someone who came all the way there.
Then that person noticed me and Shinya
and gently put a note on it.
During this time, a note came in...
What? What's this? I flipped it open.
I've been cheering for you for a while and saw you.
I thought I shouldn't call out to you.
I'll continue to support you.I will continue to support you.
Maya and Hoshina, right?
relatives
You went to Famire sometime ago.
When was it?
I took a picture with my cell phone
You took a picture, didn't you?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I'm sorry if I've mistaken you for someone else
Thank you Maya and Hoshina for always entertaining us!
The 2017 Famire was the best!
That was so long ago!
I thought it was a good time for you to come back.
I said bye bye.
I said bye bye to the person who said bye bye.
I finished the bill.
I said, "Soon.
If you see me, please come again.
Always a pleasure.
Not always.
Always, 2017.
It's a movie.
It was six years ago.
Someday... him too... again.
Hopefully we'll run into each other at a live concert.I wish I could meet you at the live concert venue.
Super Shishinsha Sending
What do you do?
What are you going to do?
What are you doing?
why?
Why?
I had no idea why you were saying that.
What are you going to do?
Do you want to make it look like a photo shoot?
Take an insert?
We're cut off.
It's cut.
It's been cut.
That's very interesting.
Very funny.
Mire-chan is like a cameraman among the older sister members.
Mire-chan is in charge of taking pictures of things.
I think I can take really good pictures of food.
I'll post the blurry ones on my instagram.
This is the Tire Sea SPF samlois I was talking about earlier.
This is moksal, which is a shoulder loin with less oil, and it's very refreshing to eat.
I'm going to grill it now.This one is baking now.
Wow! Looks delicious!
Wow, it's so cool.
Thick!
Hey, it's so thick!
Wow!
The meat looks delicious.
Looks delicious.
Nice sound!
Hey, it's slowly coming together.
When it gets this thick, I feel like I'm barbecuing.
I'm glad we're having a barbecue this year.
I wish I had barbecued.
I'm starting to feel like I wanted to barbecue.
I ate meat sashimi.
Oh, mash!
I could barbecue tires if I didn't do the Tire See Spark every year,
Before, it was from the barbecue place behind the venue for the divine banquet,
When all the adult guests came to grill there, the knives would go all the way around,
They would go around on a summer's day, but we would get bored so quickly that we started to play.
We were bored so quickly that we started playing with them,
We ate shaved ice, and we're doing this at the banquet.
It's like summer fun.
It's true. It was a divine banquet when we were teenagers, and the banquet was like a celebration.
Like a divine banquet.Like a divine banquet.
Yes! The reward is, you know, it's your job, that's what it is,
So you went to the divine banquet, like there's a live concert on the side of the reward barbecue.
I just went to two of the Xia Tian Yuan student members.
Live music is not for fun, you know.
I can't tell you, really. They were so surprised to see us on the street.
Surprised.
Wow!
What kind of set up?
Oh, wow!
This is how it's done.
Is it thick?
Even the princess's shoes.
Yay!
Wow, it's finally done!
Watching Koyasan, she's a pretty moppin' person, so she's a loose flowin' person, but..,
I think that Maya-san is an idol.
Why?
She's just so wow!
Is she reacting for TV?
She's reacting, and I think it's great.
Where did I say that?
But I think Maya-san is more surprising in her private life, too,But I'm quite surprised at Maya-san, even in her private life,
I don't think so. I'm quite private.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Delicious.
Delicious?
Yum!
Te-ryu.
Wow, what a title!
I'm really referring to Natsunaga's reactions,
It looks really delicious,
I thought it would stand out.
Delicious.
Have you ever eaten something before?
Before eating?
Yum.
That's what I was doing.
I'm doing that now.
I said it's good. Really?
Yeah, I'm sure.
It's, uh...
It looks good.
Yes, that's my daughter.
This is rice with soup stock.
This is rice with otsue.This is rice with otsue.
The rice itself has a strong aroma and flavor,
It is delicious just as it is,
I recommend this and the yuzu pepper that is recommended at Samyokka,
Oh, it's true! It smells like soup stock.
I love dashi.
Wow! Looks delicious!
I hope you enjoy it with your rice.
Thank you very much.
It's my private time.
Thank you for watching.
Looks delicious!
Let's eat!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
You've got a good appetite.
At first, you wandered off.
I forgot everything I just explained.
This is 5,000 yen for one wanderer.
This is Ueno Mokusara for one yen.
Yes, sir!
Put some yuzu kosho on it.
Put it on rice with soup stock.
Please eat it!
Please gobble it up!Please gobble it up!
Yes, sir!
It's better than the last one.
You're right, he's smart.
I'll take the first one.
I've been wandering around...
You're smart.
Why is that okay?
Are you full?
Yes, indeed.
It's the heart of Japan.
I love takikigo gohan.
It's great.
Please eat in order.
Here we go!
Cooked rice.
How is it?
I'm chewing.
Sorry, it looks like eggplant miso soup.
Eggplant miso soup.
It's kind of good, too.
It's good.
Ah!
I'm going to chew again.
I don't want to chew on the wayI don't want to chew it on the way out.
It's so good.
The meat is so tender and juicy.
And it's refreshing with water and pepper.
And the dashi broth goes so well with the rice.
You can eat all the way through without opening your mouth.
It's so refreshing.
But the meat is juicy.
Delicious!
I'd like to have some too.
Mmm.
It's refreshing.
Delicious!
It's so good!
I can eat a lot.
It's about halfway through the rice.
Rice with dashi soup is too good!
I like the yuzu rice.
It's so refreshing, the dashi broth with the water and pepper is so good.
It's not the tripod greens I know.
It's very common.
It's all the rage.
They're having an exchange match.We're playing a social game.
Yeah, we're playing a social game.
It's great.
Bon appétit.
Now?
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
You should try it.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
Thank you so much for today.
Thank you so much.
What a question we got today.
What's your favorite part about you two?
You're faster than I thought you'd be.
Really?
Oh, he's cute.
What should we do?